Kill him.
اقتله.
What are you busy with? Long time no see,
بماذا انت مشغول؟  وقت طويل لا رؤية،
Cheers,
هتافات،
Gao,
جاو
What took you so long?
ما الذي أخرك؟
Everyone is waiting for you.
الجميع في انتظارك.
Come on, let's go.
هيا بنا نذهب.
Let's go eat.
فلنذهب لنأكل.
Come on, guys.
كونوا واقعيين يا قوم.
What auction?
ما المزاد؟
Head of the Fortress,
رئيس القلعة ،
we've made a lot of money this time.
لقد كسبنا الكثير من المال هذه المرة.
I just asked around.
أنا فقط سألت من حولنا.
Cheng Dalei wants to auction his horse,
يريد Cheng Dalei بيع حصانه بالمزاد ،
starting with 20 jin of grain.
تبدأ بـ 20 جين من الحبوب.
I heard that the value of each military horse
سمعت أن قيمة كل حصان عسكري
is at least 200 jin of grain.
ما لا يقل عن 200 جين من الحبوب.
How is that possible?
كيف يعقل ذلك؟
Congratulations to Head Bai, with 30 jin of grain,
ألف مبروك لرئيس باي ، مع 30 جين من الحبوب ،
you like to bring a jade lion to Zhaoye,
تحب إحضار أسد من اليشم إلى Zhaoye ،
Congratulations.
تهانينا.
Congratulations. Thank you, Master Cheng.
تهانينا.  شكرا لك سيد تشنغ.
Ladies and gentlemen,
السيدات والسادة،
after the bidding of Village Head Bai,
بعد مناقصة رئيس القرية باي ،
I believe you all know
أعتقد أنكم تعلمون جميعًا
the rules of blind shooting.
قواعد الرماية الأعمى.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
So after the red cloth is uncovered,
لذلك بعد الكشف عن القماش الأحمر ،
whether it's a donkey or a horse,
سواء كان حمارًا أو حصانًا ،
It depends on your luck.
هذا يعتمد على حظك.
Come on. Hurry up.
تعال.  أسرع - بسرعة.
Head of the Fortress,
رئيس القلعة ،
we must shoot the next round.
يجب أن نطلق النار في الجولة التالية.
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
The underground world of martial arts
عالم تحت الأرض لفنون الدفاع عن النفس
is dangerous. This is fishing,
خطير.  هذا صيد السمك
Fishing,
صيد السمك،
Next,
التالي،
Start bidding for the second horse.
ابدأ بالمزايدة على الحصان الثاني.
The starting price is 20 jin of grain,
سعر البداية 20 جنية من الحبوب ،
30 jin,
30 جين
50 jin,
50 جين
70 jin,
70 جين
80,
80 ،
100 jin.
100 جين.
See?
يرى؟
They have been carried away
لقد تم إبعادهم
by the sweetness just now.
من حلاوة فقط الآن.
It's already done.
لقد تم بالفعل.
Cheng Dalei has started to close the net.
بدأ Cheng Dalei في إغلاق الشباك.
Head of the Fortress is indeed as good as he expected.
رأس القلعة في الواقع جيدة كما توقع.
Did Goutouling get
هل حصل Goutouling
a good horse or a bad one?
حصان جيد ام سيء؟
It's a flying electric horse,
إنه حصان كهربائي طائر ،
oh,
أوه،
It's actually a flying electric horse,
إنه في الواقع حصان كهربائي طائر ،
which is the best horse with no market price.
وهو أفضل حصان بدون سعر في السوق.
Yes.
نعم.
No,
لا،
Gosh,
يا الهي ،
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
don't take it from me later.
لا تأخذها مني لاحقا.
There are ten horses left.
بقي عشرة خيول.
Do you want to bid?
هل تريد المزايدة؟
I want them all.
أريدهم جميعا.
Did you hear it right?
هل سمعته بشكل صحيح؟
I'll take all ten of them.
سآخذ كل عشرة منهم.
But Head Gao
لكن رئيس جاو
hasn't bid yet,
لم تقدم بعد ،
That's right,
صحيح،
That's right.
صحيح.
800 jin,
800 جين
I fly tiger,
أطير النمر
Out of 800 jin of grain,
من 800 جين من الحبوب ،
bought all the ten horses.
اشترى كل الخيول العشرة.
Do you have anyone taller than me?
هل لديك أي شخص أطول مني؟
Is there?
هل هناك؟
You didn't, did you?
لم تفعل ، أليس كذلك؟
No, it belongs to me, Gao Feihu.
لا ، إنها تخصني يا غاو فيهو.
Buy it and leave!
شرائه واتركه!
Head of the Fortress,
رئيس القلعة ،
There's only 800 jin of grain in our village.
لا يوجد سوى 800 جين من الحبوب في قريتنا.
You don't know anything.
أنت لا تعرف أي شيء.
Others are greedy and I fear them.
البعض الآخر جشع وأنا أخاف منهم.
Others are afraid that I'm greedy.
يخشى الآخرون من أنني جشع.
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
Bring all my horses out.
أخرج كل خيولي.
Head Gao,
رئيس جاو ،
please
لو سمحت
reconsider it.
إعادة النظر فيه.
I'm afraid
أنا خائف
so. See?
لذا.  يرى؟
Are you scared?
هل انت خائف؟
Cut it out! Buy it
اقطعها!  اشتريها
and leave!
ويغادر!
Don't go back on your word.
لا تتراجع عن كلمتك.
The last ten horses,
آخر عشرة خيول ،
they must all be good horses at the bottom of the box.
يجب أن يكونوا جميعًا خيولًا جيدة في الجزء السفلي من الصندوق.
You can hide it from my eyes.
يمكنك إخفائها عن عيني.
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
Bring out all my good horses.
أخرج كل خيولي الجيدة.
Can the bangs look at the road?
هل يمكن للانفجارات أن تنظر إلى الطريق؟
Ouch! What a big butt!
أوتش!  يا له من مؤخرة كبيرة!
Ha ha,
هاها
Oh, it got shot.
أوه ، لقد تم إطلاق النار عليه.
Oh,
أوه،
Sweating donkey.
حمار يتصبب عرقا.
Despicable Cheng Dalei,
الحقير تشنغ دالي ،
how dare you use a bad horse.
كيف تجرؤ على استخدام حصان سيء.
You used a bad horse to lie to me,
لقد استخدمت حصانًا سيئًا لتكذب علي ،
and played with my feelings like this.
ولعبت بمشاعري هكذا.
I want to cancel the deal.
اريد الغاء الصفقة
Cancel it.
ألغها.
Since Gao Village mainly cancels the deal,
نظرًا لأن قرية Gao تلغي الصفقة بشكل أساسي ،
we'll start
سنبدأ
all the bidding again.
كل العطاءات مرة أخرى.
Trade these horses for food.
استبدل هذه الخيول بالطعام.
It turns out that everything is under Master's control.
اتضح أن كل شيء تحت سيطرة السيد.
Wonderful.
رائع.
Fragments of treasures,
شظايا من الكنوز
Master,
يتقن،
Something bad happened.
شيء ما سيء حدث.